THÔNG TIN LIÊN HÊ



 37/8H, ấp 1, xã Xuân Thới Thượng, Huyện Hóc Môn, Hồ Chí Minh, Việt Nam

THÔNG TIN CÁ NHÂN

Ngày sinh11/08/1988Quốc tịchViệt NamTình trạng hôn nhânĐã kết hônGiới tínhNam

NGƯỜI THAM KHẢO

Lindsay Nutley

Marketing Director - QLM Label Makers - QLM Group

Mark Shaw

IT Director (Australia) - ITMS Group

Trần Minh Quốc

Giám Đốc - Cổ Phần Quốc Tế Hưng Gia

Kevin Juan

IT Manager - Cathay Life Viet Nam

Đoàn Công Danh

Manager - CMC SI Sài Gòn

NGUYEN DO MINH SON

IT DIRECTOR - 11 NĂM KINH NGHIỆM

I'm a seasoned and passionate IT professional with over seven years of experience in leading and managing teams, as well as developing and delivering innovative IT solutions.

I'm excited to find a role where I can use my skills and experience to help your company achieve its goals.

KINH NGHIỆM LÀM VIỆC

TeamLeader / Manager

Hoang Ha Label Co.,LTD - QLM Label Makers / ITMS VietNam 10/2015 - 10/2023 (8 năm)

Accomplishments:

- Recruited and built a team to work on B2B solutions.
- Excelled in problem-solving, project coordination, strategic thinking, empathy, and communication.
- Developed and implemented infrastructure, network, and camera systems for the entire company and factory.

.NET & SharePoint Developer, System

Administrator

Công ty TNHH Tổng Công ty Công nghệ và Giải pháp CMC 04/2014 - 09/2015 (1 năm 5 tháng)

Responsibilities:

- Develop and maintain business core management information systems (MIS)
 - Manage, maintain, and back up Microsoft SQL Server 2012 databases
 - Provide technical support to all users for business-related issues
 - Report to manager

Accomplishments:

- Set up new modules in MIS
- Managed MS SQL database systems
- Developed knowledge of insurance core, insurance business, and banking core systems
 - Created plans for staff and discussed them with company users
 - · Committed to meeting deadlines and delivering high-quality work

Senior Java Developer

Công TY TNHH Bảo Hiểm Nhân Thọ Cathay Life Việt Nam 02/2012 - 04/2014 (2 năm 2 tháng)

Responsibilities:

- Developing the business core
- Managing, maintaining, and backing up the database (IBM DB2)
- Supporting all users about issues in business
- Reporting to your manager

Accomplishments:

- Setting up some new processes in POS & Claim Business
- Managing the IBM DB2 database system
- Gaining knowledge about the insurance core and insurance business
- · Making plans for staff and discussing them with insurance users
- · Being committed to deadlines and quality

System Administrator

Cổ Phần Quốc Tế Hưng Gia 05/2011 - 02/2012 (9 tháng)

Responsibilities:

- Manage the IT room
- Manage, maintain, and back up the database (MS SQL Server)
- · Issue and control admin forms
- · Report to manager

Accomplishments:

- Set up the process for the website
- Managed the SQL database system
- Gained experience in internet, HTML, and CSS, and managed them all independently
- Developed some knowledge of FTP, business plans for business websites, and staff planning
 - · Committed to deadlines and quality

HỌC VẤN

Odoo - All versions

Khác - https

01/2020 - 10/2023 (3 năm 9 tháng)

Salesforce Certified Administrator

Khác - http://certi

09/2017 - 09/2017

Salesforce Certified Administrator

Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I

Khác - http://certi

08/2017 - 08/2017

Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I

Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder

Khác - http://certi

08/2017 - 08/2017

Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder

SharePoint

Cử nhân - Microsoft

09/2014 - 09/2014

Tín chỉ MCPD on SharePoint 2010

IT

Cao đẳng - FPT Aptech

06/2009 - 04/2011 (1 năm 10 tháng)

2009 - 2011

FPT Aptech - HCM, Vietnam

Diploma in Information System Management (Graduated - 2011) Higher Diploma in Software Engineering (Graduated - 2011)

0 1				
CIID	100tc	CTILO	$\square \cap \square$	
. אווור	ects	SILL	пеп	

- Operating Systems : Window
- Programming languages : ASP, ,C#,Java.
- Databases : MS SQL Server , IBM DB2.
- And subjects: System Analysis and Design, Software Project Management,

Object - Oriented Programming(using C# language, using Java language),

Database Management System, Design and develop website

• After once subjects I must make a project for close.

	_
KỸ NĂNG	
ERP Management	
Ideas Brainstorming	
Human Management	
Odoo ERP	
Infrastructure Management	
Innovation in Work	
Decision Making	
IT Budget Control	
Strategic Thinking	
Conflict Resolution	
Problem Solving	
Communication	
IT Recruitment	
Project Management	
Leadership	
NGOẠI NGỮ	
Tiếng Anh	
CHỨNG CHỈ	

Salesforce Certified Platform App Builder

Salesforce - 2017

https: fication-detail-prin...

Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I

Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I	
Salesforce - 2017	
https:	fication-detail-prin
Salesforce Certified Administrator	
Salesforce - 2017	
https:	fication-detail-prin